Objective:
Enter the enemy base and make your way to where their flag resides in the tower. Grab it and bring it back to the base of your tower. 
Place it on the raised square to capture it. The flag will then return to the enemy base. 

Scoring:
1 point per capture. 

Notes:
Flag carriers drop the flag when they die.
Dropped flags return to their base after 60 seconds.

-----------------------

Map by PJX 2013